JAN CZIZIKOW



PERSONAL DETAILS

- **□** 12 June 1992
- Polish
 Po
- · +(86) 131-6700-7112
- □ jan_czizikow@hotmail.com
- www.janczizikow.com

PROFILE

Currently a senior undergraduate business student in Donghua University, living in China since 2012. Passionate about marketing, PR, branding and serious about future career in related business field. Highly motivated, proactive and adaptable fast-learner, eager to further develop his skills through a challenging experience. I believe that education is based on two pillars: theory and practice, thus, I engaged in a couple of part-time positions through studies.

EXPERIENCE

Social Cloud China

Full & Part-time / 1 year July 2015 - May 2016

Winwho Technology

Part-time / 4 months March 2015 - June 2015

Fujian Hotel

Full-time / 2 months July 2014 - 2014 August

Marketing Assistant

- Assisted in developing marketing campaigns
- Assisted in organizing events and press conferences
- Created and maintained relationships and partnerships with media and sponsors
- Organized and attended meetings with clients and potential partners
- Compiled reports and marketing materials (newsletters, social media content, press releases, brochures, posters)

Event Marketing Intern

- Assisted in planning, organizing and implementation of online and offline events
- Product and brand promotion via public relation activities
- Edited, maitaned and updated "财神所聘 / Caishen Locksreen" app wallpapers

Hotel Guest Relation Officer

- Offered assistance and provided needed or sought information to the guests
- Solicited guest responses, concerning their satisfaction and complaints
- Conducted inspections of the lobby, monitored officers, reported unusual occurrences, handled lost-and-found matters

EDUCATION

Donghua University, China

2014 - Present

Beijing Language and Culture University, China

2012 - 2014

Bachelor of Business Administration

- GPA 3.2/ 4.0
- English-taught Business degree with Chinese courses

Chinese Language Studies

- Mastered 2,500 commonly used words and related grammar patterns
- Passed HSK5 with a total score of 235/300 06.2014

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Languages

Polish: Native Russian: Bilingual English: Fluent

Chinese (Mandarin): Proficient

Knowledge

Social Media Marketing Marketing Communications Public Relations

Technical

Microsoft Office: Advanced HTML5 & CSS3: Intermediate Adobe Photoshop: Basic Adobe Illustrator: Basic

Interests

Traveling Skateboarding Digital Marketing & Web Design

REFEREES

Ambra Schillirò

Director of Social Cloud
□ +(86) 158-2112-2831
□ ambra.schilliro@socialcloudchina.com

Marko Ljubičič

Professor at Donghua University

□ (+86) 150-2124-2364

□ mr.ljubicic@gmail.com

JAN CZIZIKOW



基本情况

- ☎ 1992年06月12日
- № 波兰
- **+**(86) 131-6700-7112
- □ jan_czizikow@hotmail.com
- www.janczizikow.com

职业概要

自2012生活在中国,目前东华大学本科商科学生。热衷于市场营销,公关,品牌推广等相关业务领域的未来事业。积极进取,适应能力强的学习者,希望能通过更具有挑战性的经历来进一步发展各项技能。相信教育是建立在两个支柱之上的:理论和实践,因此在他在校期间也从事过相关兼职已获得更多实践经验。

工作经历

Social Cloud China

全职和兼职 / 1年 2015年7月 - 2016年5月

仁画科技

兼职 / 4个月 2015年3月 - 2015年6月

富建酒店

全职 / 2个月 2014年7月 - 2014年8月

市场助理

- · Assisted in developing marketing campaigns
- Assisted in organizing events and press conferences
- Created and maintained relationships and partnerships with media and sponsors
- Organized and attended meetings with clients and potential partners
- Compiled reports and marketing materials (newsletters, social media content, press releases, brochures, posters)

活动策划实习生

- Assisted in planning, organizing and implementation of online and offline events
- Product and brand promotion via public relation activities
- Edited, maitaned and updated "财神所聘 / Caishen Locksreen" app wallpapers

宾客关系主任实习生

- Offered assistance and provided needed or sought information to the guests
- Solicited guest responses, concerning their satisfaction and complaints
- Conducted inspections of the lobby, monitored officers, reported unusual occurrences, handled lost-and-found matters

教育背景

东华大学,中国

2014 - 至今

北京语言大学,中国

2012 - 2014

工商管理(本科)

- GPA 3.2/ 4.0
- •英语授课本科商科项目

汉语进修

- 掌握2,500个常用词语
- 通过HSK5级, 总成绩(235/300) 06.2014

个人技能

语言技能

波兰语: 母语 俄罗斯语: 双语技能 英语: 高级(商务会话) 中文: 中级(日常会话)

专业技能

社会媒体营销 营销传播 公共关系

技术技能

Microsoft Office: 高级 HTML5 & CSS3: 中级 Adobe Photoshop: 基本 Adobe Illustrator: 基本

兴趣爱好

旅游 滑板

数字营销,网页设计

证明人

Ambra Schillirò

Director of Social Cloud
□ +(86) 158-2112-2831
□ ambra.schilliro@socialcloudchina.com

Marko Ljubičič

东华大学教授

- o (+86) 150-2124-2364
- mr.ljubicic@gmail.com